
[
    {
      "question": "안녕하세요",
      "answer": "Hello"
    },
    {
      "question": "감사합니다",
      "answer": "Thank you"
    },
    {
      "question": "천만에요",
      "answer": "You’re welcome"
    },
    {
      "question": "잠시만요",
      "answer": "Excuse me"
    },
    {
      "question": "괜찮아요",
      "answer": "Okay"
    },
    {
      "question": "죄송합니다",
      "answer": "I’m sorry"
    },
    {
      "question": "주세요",
      "answer": "Please give me"
    },
    {
      "question": "몰라요",
      "answer": "I don’t know"
    },
    {
      "question": "알아요",
      "answer": "I know"
    },
    {
      "question": "이해해요",
      "answer": "I understand"
    },
    {
      "question": "좋아요",
      "answer": "Good"
    },
    {
      "question": "안 좋아요",
      "answer": "Not good"
    }
  ]
  